carefreeliners.com 2015-12-07

# Edgewell Personal Care - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our websites.  Edgewell Personal Care Company (“Edgewell”) and its affiliates own and operate the websites listed [here](http://edgewell.com/privacy-policy/#appendix-a) and the microsites that link to this Privacy Policy. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to all of the companies in our corporate group as “Edgewell”, “we”, or “us”.  

This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your personal information is collected and used through the websites.    

#### What Information Do We Collect from You?

You may browse many sections of the websites without providing any personal information about yourself.    However, if you choose to register for one of our promotions or services, ask us a question through our Contact Us link, apply for employment with us, or apply to become an approved supplier, we must collect certain information from you. 

#### Registration

To register on our websites, you must complete the registration process by providing personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email, telephone number or mobile phone number, as well as information relating to what you would like to receive from us.  If you choose to register, you may also be asked to choose a user name and password.  Please keep this information secure.  If you choose to register, you have the right to unsubscribe from certain communications from us at any time by contacting us through one of the contact options provided below (email, letter or telephone). Please give us a reasonable amount of time to process your unsubscribe request.

#### Employment

If you apply for a job with Edgewell through our websites, the information collected will include your qualifications for the position, your education, applicable licenses or certifications, prior job history, references, and any other information that you choose to include about yourself. 

#### Supplier Portal

If you apply to become an approved supplier, the information we collect will include relevant business information, such as the name, contact details, location and products or services offered by your organization, and information relating to pricing, sourcing, and other business practices. We may also request additional information from you, including an on-site audit or additional checking to ensure that our prospective partnership with you will be consistent with Edgewell’s business, legal and compliance expectations for our partners. If you become an approved supplier, we will also require other relevant information from you that is relevant to our ongoing business relationship.

#### Newsletter and Email Communications

If you choose to sign up for our newsletter or email communications online, you must submit certain basic information during the registration process.  This information may include your name, email address, and a confirmation that you are over 18 years old.  This information is used to send the newsletter or email communications electronically, and to provide you with customer service and respond to your inquiries.

#### Surveys

While visiting certain portions of the websites, you may be given the opportunity to provide feedback regarding various Edgewell products.  You may be given opportunities to rate Edgewell products and to publicly ask and answer questions pertaining to Edgewell products.  In order to fully participate in these portions of the websites, you will be asked to provide your full name and an email address, as well as an online username which will be publicly linked to your product ratings, questions, answers and other comments.  You will be required to agree to a set of terms and conditions. You may also be prompted to submit additional voluntary information, such as specific age range, gender, location, address, phone number, website, job title, and the length of time which you have used Edgewell products.  This information may be linked online to your chosen username.  Edgewell stores this additional information, if provided, and later uses it to help us better understand and respond to the collective feedback we receive.  

Occasionally, we may invite you to participate in a survey or poll such as providing feedback on our websites’ site content, services, or products. Your responses will be anonymous unless you choose to provide your contact details so that we can provide you with additional information regarding the survey or poll.  

#### Surveys

While visiting certain portions of the website, you may be given the opportunity to provide feedback regarding various Energizer products. You may be given opportunities to rate Energizer products and to publicly ask and answer questions pertaining to Energizer products. In order to fully participate in these portions of the website, you will be asked to provide your full name and an email address, as well as a created online username which will be publicly linked to your product ratings, questions, answers and other comments. You will be required to agree to a set of terms and conditions which require, among other things, you to verify that you are over the age of 13. You may also be prompted to submit additional voluntary information, such as specific age range, gender, location, address, phone number, website, job title, and the length of time which you have used Energizer products. This information may be linked online to your chosen username. Energizer stores this additional information, if provided, and later uses it to help us better understand and respond to the collective feedback we receive.

Occasionally, we may invite you to participate in a survey or poll such as providing feedback on our website site content, services, or products. Your responses will be anonymous unless you choose to provide your contact details so that we can provide you with additional information regarding the survey or poll.

For any information that we collect through our sites, Energizer becomes the owner of that data.

#### Cookies and Other Web Tracking Techniques 

Like most websites, we use “cookies” on our websites to help us serve you better on future visits, and to help us analyze web traffic for our websites, and evaluate and improve the content or functions of our websites.  A cookie is a small text file which is sent by a website, accepted by a web browser and then placed on your hard drive.  The information collected from cookies sent by Edgewell and approved third parties assisting us with our websites lets us know that you visited our websites in the past, and helps you avoid having to re-enter information on each visit in order to use some of our products or services.  Cookies also help us analyze use of our websites, and better aggregate useful information when users provide feedback about our websites or products. You may be able to set your browser to refuse all cookies from this and other websites that you visit.  This will provide you with more control over the acceptance of cookies on your hard drive.  However, it is possible that some portions of the websites will not function properly or may perform more slowly if you choose to reject cookies.  By using our websites and not disabling cookies, you consent to allowing their use for the described purposes. Remember also that disabling cookies is browser specific.  If you log on using Internet Explorer, you must also disable cookies in Safari if you use that browser at a different time. We may also collect information about your method of access such as your operating system (Windows 7, Windows 8, Mac, Linux, etc.) and your browser (Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Safari, etc.).  We may use access method information along with information about site searches you run to serve you personalized content using third party vendors such as Sitefinity. 

We may use third-party web analytics services on our websites, such as those of Google Analytics. The analytics providers that administer these services use technologies such as cookies to help us analyze how visitors use the websites. The information collected through these technologies (including IP address) is disclosed to these analytics providers, who use the information to evaluate use of the websites. To learn more about Google Analytics and how to opt out, please visit [www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers.  Our websites do not support DNT codes.  However, except in the case of analytic cookies and social networking platforms described herein, our websites limit tracking to the internal uses described above and does not enable the tracking of our users across multiple websites.  Except in the case of analytics cookies and social networking platforms described herein, our website does not track your use across multiple websites, however, other websites to which we link may.  Please review their privacy policies to understand how you may be tracked.

#### Social Platform Registrations and Social Media Plugins

Some of the Edgewell websites permit you to use a third party social networking platforms such as Facebook, Pinterest, Twitter and Google+.  This includes use of social media plugins such as Facebook “Like”, Tweet, Pinterest “Pin,” Google “+1” buttons, etc. When you use these social networking platforms and plugins, your username and password for the services and other information available about you or collected from you on these services may be shared with us. We may ask your permission to repost your Facebook or Twitter quotes on our websites.  If you agree, you grant us the right to use your posts on our websites for promotional purposes.  

When you use social networking platforms and plugins, you share your information with them and their privacy policy and applicable terms of use apply to the use and disclosure of such information. In addition, they may be able to collect information about you, including your activity on the Edgewell websites, and they may notify your connections on the social networking platform about your use of the Edgewell websites. Such services may allow your activity to be monitored across multiple websites for purposes of delivering more targeted advertising. Please note that their privacy policies and applicable terms of use may apply and we encourage you to read them. We may add new social networking plugins and buttons to our websites from time to time. 

#### Using, Sharing and Transferring Information Collected

Edgewell may share your information within the Edgewell group of companies as well as with third-party service providers that assist us with our websites, contests and sweepstakes, such as in providing the products or services that you requested, or for the purposes of improving our marketing or administration.  This includes companies that provide analytics to us about use of our websites, so that we can evaluate use of our websites and continue to improve our websites’ content. 

Our U.S. websites are intended for residents of the U.S.   If you happen to live in another country yet use our U.S. websites, any data collected about you with respect to your use of our websites will be transferred to the U.S. As such, please note that there may be different standards that apply to how your data may be used and protected than the standards in place in your country.  Nevertheless, Edgewell has put in place safeguards to protect your data irrespective of the country from which it originates. 

Except as provided below in “Promotions and Third Parties,” Edgewell does not share or sell any personal information that you provide to us through our websites for any separate use by any third party for its own purposes.  However, from time to time, we may provide aggregate (statistical) information about our customers, sales, online traffic patterns and related information to third parties who help us improve our business and services, but these statistics do not include any personally identifying information.  

In the event that we sell, assign or transfer all or part of the Edgewell business (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation), we may transfer your personal information to a third party. 

#### Promotions and Third Parties

From time to time, Edgewell may run promotions offering special deals, coupons, discounts, chances to win contests, and other prizes.  These promotions may involve third-parties.  In order to participate in these promotions, Edgewell may request certain basic information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, and date of birth.  This and other information provided to participate in the promotions may be processed by Edgewell in order to help us better understand how we can design and market our products for you and others. This information may also be shared with any relevant third-party promotional partners involved in the specific promotion for which you choose to sign-up.  In addition, certain third-party promotional partners may use your information to contact you in order to provide you with more information about their company and with further opportunities to make additional purchases. Please remember that Edgewell is not responsible for the information practices of third parties to whom you choose to disclose information.

#### Safeguarding Your Information

Edgewell maintains physical, technical, and administrative safeguards that are designed to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized alteration, theft, unauthorized access, and unauthorized disclosure. 

#### Children's Privacy

Our websites are not intended for use by children under the age of 13.  Edgewell does not market any of its products online for children under the age of 13, nor does Edgewell design its online applications, advertisements and other features to attract an audience of children under the age of 13.  Although certain pages within the websites may reference “kids,” “children,” or “students,” Edgewell strictly intends for such portions of the websites to be used only by adults (such as parents and teachers) or children of the age 13 or older.  Edgewell does not knowingly register or otherwise collect personally identifiable information from any child under the age of 13. 

#### Update, Modify or Correct Your Information 

We encourage you to contact us to update or correct your information if it changes or if you believe that any information that we have collected about you is inaccurate.  To the extent provided by the law of your jurisdiction, Edgewell also permits you to obtain a copy of personal information that we hold about you.  To do so, please email us at webmaster@edgewell.com, or write to us at:  Edgewell Headquarters, Timberlake Corporate Center III, 1350 Timberlake Manor Parkway, Chesterfield, MO 63017, ATTN: edgewell.com.

Please note that we will likely require additional information from you in order to honor the request, such as to ensure proper authentication or to verify to which Edgewell company the information was provided.

#### Right to Unsubscribe

You have the right to unsubscribe from certain services that we offer.  To do so, please use our Contact Us link on the websites for additional information, or email us at webmaster@ edgewell.com.  Please note that if you already have requested products or services when you decide to withdraw consent, there may be a short period of time for us to update your preferences and ensure that we honor your request.

#### Links to Other Websites 

Our websites may contain links to websites operated, controlled and maintained by independent third parties. We do not control the use of information you may provide to such third parties. If you access other websites using the links provided in our websites, the operators of the third-party sites may collect information from you which will then be used by them in accordance with their own privacy policies, not ours. Those policies may differ from ours. It is your responsibility to familiarize yourself with privacy policies on our websites and other websites.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

As we continue to provide additional services and as the privacy laws and regulations evolve, it may be necessary to revise or update this Policy.  We encourage you to review this Policy from time to time, as you return to our websites, so that you are familiar with any changes.  For significant changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our websites indicating at the top of the Policy when it was most recently updated.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions, please email us at webmaster@edgewell.com or write to us at:  Edgewell Headquarters, Timberlake Corporate Center III, 1350 Timberlake Manor Parkway, Chesterfield, MO 63017,  ATTN: edgewell.com, or call us at: (314) 594-1900.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to privacy@edgewell.com, or write to us at: Edgewell Headquarters, Timberlake Corporate Center III, 1350 Timberlake Manor Parkway, Chesterfield, MO 63017,  ATTN: edgewell.com, or call us at: (314) 594-1900. 

© 2015 Edgewell Personal Care Company.  All Rights Reserved.
